麦克斯 你会怎么描述我们的公寓
Okay, Max. How would you describe our apartment?
不许说
And I've already ruled out
"比《沉默的羔羊》里的囚禁井还可怕"
"worse than that girl-pit in Silence of the Lambs."
被关在里面的女的偶尔还能"沉默"[清静]一会呢
Well, at least she had some silence once in awhile.
听着 不会有人愿意花钱来住这垃圾堆
Look, no one's gonna pay money to rent this dump.
连我们自己都六个月没付钱了
We haven't in six months.
最近每个在威廉斯堡的人
Everyone else in Williamsburg is making money
都在"寻找奇居网"出租他们的破房子
renting their crappy places on Airbnb.
就看你怎么描述美化它
It's all how you describe it.
快来发挥骗功吧
So let's start lying.
这主意太棒了 我超想做呢
This is a fantastic idea and I really want to do this.
第一个问题"描述一下周围环境"
First question: "Describe your neighborhood."
房子破烂 鼠辈横行
Run-down with a bunch of rats.
古色古香
Old-world charm.
欢迎宠物
Pet-friendly.
"描述附近居民"
"What type of people live there?"
毒虫 妓女 流浪汉
Junkies, whores, homeless.
演员
Actors.
"家里有浴缸吗"
"Do you have a hot tub?"
有时候
Sometimes.
"健身房"呢
"Gym?"
俩 楼上的基佬阿"健"
Two. Gay Jim upstairs,
以及对门的直男阿"健"
and straight Jim across the hall
他只有喝醉时才是基佬
who's only gay when he's drunk.
"房子的出租时间
"When is your space available?
永远 有时候 就一次"
Always, sometimes, one time."
就像我们的性生活一样
Oh, just like our sex lives.
我"永远"有得搞 "有时候"无聊也搞
Always for me, sometimes out of boredom,
以及你的"就一次"
and one time for you.
厄尔 猜猜我跟麦克斯干什么了
Earl, guess what Max and I did.
我只知道你们有什么没干
I know what you didn't do.
没清理甜品展示柜
Clean this dessert carousel.
里面的拿破仑蛋糕从拿破仑时代就在里面了
There's a napoleon in here since Napoleon.
我们在寻找奇居[阿拉伯]网上出租了公寓
We rented our apartment on Airbnb.
租给阿拉伯人吗
You rented to Arabs?
租出去容易 收回来难啊
Well, good luck getting it back.
他们的领域保护性有点强啊
They tend to be a tad territorial.
这网站是登记房源 出租给外地旅客
Airbnb is an agency that rents to out-of-towners
我猜还有本地搞外遇找炮房的男人吧
and I'm guessing local men cheating on their wives.
我做好啦
Well, I did it.
我知道
I know.
你18岁的时候跟英国哈里王子"做"的嘛
When you were 18 with Prince Harry.
反正你是这么跟我说的
Or so you say.
有三组人想租我们的公寓
We have three offers for our apartment.
怎么可能
How?
让我重新措辞一遍
Let me rephrase that.
咋整的啊
How!
我想到了完美的推销标语
I found the perfect sales pitch.
"欢迎入住世间梦想死去之地"吗
"Stay at the place where dreams die"?
"体验最真实的威廉斯堡生活"
"Have the authentic Williamsburg experience."
你是指会被看起来像
Oh, you mean getting clumsily felt up
淘金潮年代来的人上下其手浑身揩油吗
by a guy who looks like he came from the gold rush?
谁都可以住到酒店
Anyone can stay at a hotel.
但有多少人有机会说 去纽约玩时
But how often can you say you went to New York
住到了一间"布鲁克林的波西米亚风带马厩
and stayed at a "Brooklyn Bohemian barn apartment
以及马匹的公寓"呢
with a live-in horse"?
妹子 你可真能吹啊
Girl, you are good.
所以我们现在选租给谁就行了
So now we just have to pick who gets our apartment.
一个想抛开一切的男人
A guy looking to get away from it all.
这人是想自杀
That's a suicide.
有道理 我们骗人 他们也能骗人
You're right. We lie, they lie.
一对已婚夫妇想重燃爱火
Um, a married couple looking to reconnect.
谋杀后自杀
Murder-suicide.
最后一组 时尚模特好友们
And finally, a girls' getaway weekend
想过一个愉快的周末假期
for some fashion model friends.
一帮死肥妞想要"谋杀"
A couple of chubby girls looking to murder
一桶又一桶的冰淇淋
some pints of Ben and Jerry's.
再吃点芝士通心粉自杀 想"饱死"自己
With maybe a sui-side of mac and cheese.
大家安安
Hey, everybody.
天寒地冻气温直降
Yeah, the temperature be droppin'
街上婊子奶头直硬
And the bitches be nippin'.
老娘要杯热巧克力
I need a hot chocolate.
美人要的热辣巧克力在此
I'm right, Sophie.
我也在此呢 厄尔
And I'm right here, Earl.
我懂你 谁都忍不住
I mean, I get it,
但朋友妻不可戏啊 兄弟
But bro code, man.
大新闻宣布
Well, big news.
我要去旅游[吸毒]
I'm going on a trip.
迷幻蘑菇还是迷幻药
Mushrooms or acid?
我要去佛蒙特州玩
I'm going to Vermont!
你要出远门啊
Oh, you're gonna be gone?
能不能让我们到你们家住两天呢
Would you mind letting us stay upstairs at your place?
我们要把公寓短租出去
We're renting out our apartment.
你们要把那垃圾堆租出去啊
You're renting out that dump?
是电视台要在你们家拍摄《幸存者》吗
Oh, are they filming Survivor at your place?
那帮废物还多久到
So when are these losers arriving?
人家才不是废物
They're not losers.
只是付钱想在我们公寓里欢度周末的姑娘们
They're just girls paying us to have a fun weekend in our apartment.
真是够废的了
What losers!
一听就是只挖冰淇淋界一霸的肥猪手
Now that is a hand that's scooped some ice cream.
你们好
Hi,
你是卡洛琳吗
are you Caroline?
天啊 她们真的是模特
Oh, my God. They really are models.
你好 我叫莉莉
Hi, I'm Lily.
靠 我被掰弯了
Oh shoot, now I'm gay.
莉莉 你是莉莉·奥尔德里奇吗
Lily? As in Lily Aldridge?
我叫玛莎
And I'm Martha.
亨特 玛莎·亨特与莉莉·奥尔德里奇吗
Hunt? Martha Hunt and Lily Aldridge?
麦克斯 你知道她们是谁吗
Max, do you know who they are?
当然啦
Sure do.
那妞就是我甩了这妞的原因
This one is the girl that I leave this one for.
不是啦 麦克斯 她们全是维多利亚的秘密模特
No, Max, they're all Victoria's Secret models.
我们想在出发去伦敦前在纽约玩两天
Yeah, we all wanted to hang out in New York before we leave for London.
我们之后要在那里走秀
We're doing a fashion show there.
我在商场里维密的店里做过一天
I worked at the Victoria's Secret at the mall for one day.
结果因为在丁字裤区吃中餐外卖就被炒了
Got fired for eating Panda Express over the thongs.
她叫麦克斯 我叫卡洛琳
This is Max. I'm Caroline.
我也曾有钱任性过
I used to be rich.
不知为何就想说一声
I just felt like I needed to say that.
她们是我们的朋友
And these are our friends,
佩特拉 盖比瑞拉 还有丽娜
Petra, Gabriella, and Rina.
你们好
Hi.
名字刚好都跟哥伦布当年的船名一样 不容易啊
What are the odds you're all named after Columbus's ships.
请进 欢迎来到"体验威廉斯堡之旅"
Come in. Welcome to "The Williamsburg experience."
房子比照片上看起来大呢
It's bigger than it looks in the photo.
我把房间的照片"修了修"
Well, I shaved of a couple of inches for the photo.
你们肯定懂的嘛
You know the drill.
所以你们为啥要来住这
So why the hell are you staying here?
想先为年华老去的未来做准备训练吗
Is this training for when your looks run out?
你看 厨房好有爱
Oh, look. The kitchen is so cute!
请问你们都瞎了 是怎么走T台的
Question: how do you walk the runway blind?
是因为我们每次都是住在同样的四季酒店
It's just that we stay at the same Four Seasons all the time.
在我们这里 因为恒温器坏了
Well, you will experience at least two seasons here,
你们能体验到两季
'cause the thermostat's broken.
外面摄氏四度 里面摄氏38度
It's 40 outside and 100 in here.
就像广告里写的 这里就是桑拿区
So as advertised, this is our sauna.
而我们波西米亚风的马厩就在那门外
And our Bohemian barn's right out that door.
往温度低的方向走就对了
Just follow the temperature drop.
麦克斯 超模要住在我们的公寓里
Max, super models are staying at our apartment.
太高兴了 我要告诉我所有的朋友
It's so exciting, I want to tell all my friends.
好像全说完了
I guess I just did.
你们已经见到栗宝了
I see you met Chestnut.
那鬃毛是真的 不是接发哦
That's his real mane, not extensions.
如广告上写的 醉人的天井
Also per our ad, a charming skylight.
让你想坐下来看看星空
In case you want to sit under the stars
享受一点祥和与安静的时光
and have a little peace and quiet.
姑娘们
Hey, girls!
赶紧上来啦
Come up already.
我要出发去参加我的大学同学会了
I want to get to my college reunion.
你们能相信我都毕业十年了吗
Can you believe it's been 10 years?
光阴是贱
Wow, time sure does lie--
我是说 光阴似箭啊
I mean, fly.
你们还跟邻居说话的啊
You talk to your neighbors?
有一次我跟我的邻居说话 结果过没多久
I talked to my neighbor once and the next thing you know,
我就收到邻居娜奥米·沃茨的长信
I have this long letter from Naomi Watts
里面写"离我老公远点"
saying, "Leave my husband alone."
我们已经认识了有五分钟这么久了
So we've known each other like five minutes already.
我的免费胸罩呢
Where's my free bra?
我这件胸罩破烂到只剩框架了
I mean, all that's left of this one is the frames.
相信我 这里面像脱衣舞娘秀一样
Trust me, it's like a burlesque show under here.
苏菲的公寓真棒
Sophie's apartment is amazing.
感觉像复活节兔子跟黄金女郎交配后的产品
It looks like an easter bunny banged a golden girl.
她的莲蓬头真是棒呆了
That was some showerhead.
我愿意嫁给它 可是它已离不开...
I'd marry it, but it's already attached...
那面墙
to the wall.
麦克斯
Max?
这里
Here!
躺这床感觉像又回到妈妈的子宫里一样
Oh, this bed is like being in the womb
而且没有那些二手烟
without all the second-hand smoke.
玛莎跟莉莉人好好啊
Martha and Lily were super-sweet.
好高兴又回到了跟明星玩的生活
So exciting to be back hanging with celebrities.
是啊 这样你终于能有些新的明星趣闻
Yeah and maybe now you can get a new celebrity story.
我早听腻你说你曾经被人说过背影
I was getting really tired of hearing how someone thought
看起来跟格温妮斯·帕特洛像的事了
you were Gwyneth Paltrow from behind.
听了还是很爽
Still flattering.
欢笑声
Laughter?
从我们的公寓里传来吗
Coming from our apartment?
你觉得她们是在笑什么呢
What do you think they're laughing at?
估计是看到了我们提款机收据上的余额吧
Probably found our account balance on an ATM slip.
我猜是玛莎说了什么好玩的事
I bet Martha said something funny.
她好有趣
She's hilarious.
漂亮到像她这样
You know, for someone who's so pretty,
靠脸吃饭就行了 都不需要啥个性
she never had to develop a personality.
我要去看看
I'm gonna go see.
麦克斯 推我一把
Max, give me a shove.
带你到最终的悬崖之前 练习一下也不错
This is good practice for the eventual cliff.
啤酒跟天使羽翼
Beers and wings.
这样才叫派对嘛
Now it's a party.
麦克斯 我们在楼下热到不行的时候
Max, you know how when it gets hot down there,
不是会满身大汗的坐着把电扇朝"小妹妹"吹吗
we just sit, sweat, and point the fan at our junk?
人家的做法有些不同哦
They do it a little differently.
她们穿着内衣裤跳舞
They are dancing in their underwear,
然后一边喝啤酒
drinking beers.
哪又如何 街角那户的男人整天这样
So? The guy on the corner does that all the time.
我的眼睛都离不开那些啤酒了
I can't take my eyes off those beers.
你们好啊
Hey! Hi, you guys.
你们想下楼
You wanna come down,
喝点啤酒 凉快一下吗
and have some beers, and cool off?
马上下来
Be right down!
现在我也好想有那些翅膀 好能快点飞到
Now I wish I had those wings, I could get down there faster.
所以这个大新闻是什么
Okay. So what is this big news?
卫生检查员发现
Did the health inspector find out
我们蟹肉棒里其实是用猫肉了吗
that the imitation crab meat is cat?
我们的是人造猫肉好吗
Technically, it's imitation cat,
不过我们今天要宣布的不是这个
but that's not what we're announcing.
我到了
I'm here.
有屁快放 我有事忙着呢
And make this snappy. I'm in the middle of something.
忙着青春期吗
Puberty?
不是 我刚才在跟奇人异事博物馆通电话
No. I was on a call with Ripley's believe it or not
告诉他们你们还在这工作 没被炒
to inform them that you still work here.
奇人异事博物馆都不信了呢
And they didn't believe it.
是这样的 我们有朋友想来店里用餐
Okay. We have some friends coming in for a meal
我们不想你们让我们丢人 或反应过激
and we don't want you guys to embarrass us and overreact.
亲爱的 我从不反应过激
Darlin', I don't overreact.
我都70好几了 还有心脏毛病的病史
I'm 70-something years old with a history of heart trouble.
我随时保持自制
I keep it in check.
麦克斯 卡洛琳
Hey, Max! Caroline!
而且口袋里随身带着心脏病药
And I keep my heart pills in my pocket.
先走一步了 虽然我很享受这美景
Excuse me, much as I enjoy the view,
但我还想听到知名气象主播给我"百岁祝寿"
I really want that "100th birthday" shout out from Al Roker.
是的 她们是维秘的模特以及我们的朋友
Yes, they're Victoria's Secret models and our friends.
昨晚我们玩到好晚 一起说凯特·摩丝的坏话
Last night we all stayed up late trashing Kate Moss.
模特来我的餐厅里
Models in my diner!
惨了 今天穿这件毛衣是错的
Oh, no. I wore the wrong sweater vest.
你的那张脸 身材与个性也都是错的
You also wore the wrong face, body, and personality.
麦克斯 我们去打招呼吧
Max, let's go say hi.
我看起来如何
How do I look?
像个服务员
Like a waitress.
妈的 全怨这身制服对吗
Damn it, it's the waitress uniform, isn't it?
你们好啊 好姐妹们
What's up, homies?
你们好吗 好姐妹们
What's up, homie?
我又爱上了我的生活
I love my life again.
从我们初次相遇已经过了一整天了
Well, it's been a whole day since we met,
我的免费胸罩呢
So where's that free bra?
-麦克斯 -干嘛
- Max! - What?
这件离死期不远了
This one's on it's last legs.
昨晚我听它在咳嗽呢
Last night I heard it coughing.
我也不介意来点新内裤
Could also use some new underwear.
我的破到剩几根纤维了
Mine are running on fumes.
我刚跟大卫发完短信
I just texted David.
他会来哦
He's coming.
这派对一定会很赞
This is going to be an amazing party.
要开派对吗
Party?
对啊 我们邀请了一些朋友过来
Yeah. We're having some friends over.
酷啊
Cool.
-是吗 -是啊
-Yeah? - Yeah.
麦克斯说了"酷啊" 是不是...
And like Max said, "Cool!"
天啊 别这样
Jeez, pull it back.
索菲亚走红毯时都没你这么想得到人注意
You're acting needier than Sofia Vergara on a red carpet.
粉丝
Big fan.
超超粉你们
Big, big fan.
本大厨请你们吃
Compliments of the chef.
我的招牌菜 冰棒
My specialty, popsicles.
我建议你们享用时 慢慢吸吮
I find they taste best when sucked slowly,
多用你们的舌头 对着厨房的方向吃
using plenty of tongue, facing the kitchen.
真不敢相信我们居然没有获邀
I can't believe we're not invited
家里第二次这么多人的派对
to the biggest party in our apartment
上一次还是蚂蚁发现你的糖豆时 它们办的呢
since those ants found your jelly beans.
哟呵
Yoo-hoo!
你们好呀 我们在楼上玩呢
Hi, so we're just up here hangin' out.
自己找乐子哦
Doin' our thang.
抱歉 姑娘 我们吵醒你们了吗
Oh, sorry, girl. Did we wake you?
快回去睡觉吧
Go back to sleep.
"快回去睡觉"
"Go back to sleep"?
她为什么会觉得我们这么逊呢
Why does she think we're so lame?
谁知道啊
Um, I don't know.
或许是因为你刚说了一些老土的字眼吧
Maybe it's 'cause you're throwing around words
比如"哟呵"和"乐子"
like "Yoo-hoo" and "thang,"
就像老妈给女儿的睡衣派对
like a mom bringing Cheetos
送浪味仙一样土到掉渣
down to a slumber party.
这事怨你
This is your fault.
她们本来挺喜欢我们 结果你一个劲儿地求胸罩
They were obsessed with us until you started asking for bras
就像无罩可穿无家可归的乞丐一样
like some bra-less homeless person.
音乐这么大声 怎么睡啊
We're never gonna sleep with all that music.
打开床头柜看看 苏菲肯定有耳塞
Check the drawer, Sophie must have ear plugs.
毕竟她住在你的正上方嘛
I mean, she lives upstairs from you.
我找到了 但我想不是拿来"塞"耳朵的
I found plugs, but I don't think they're for your ears.
没关系 我们就下去跟她们打声招呼而已
It's fine, we'll just pop downstairs and say hello.
时尚趴我最懂行了
Fashion's my scene.
是呀 你还懂买衣服不摘价签呢
Know what I'm seeing? That price tag.
快塞回去 这衣服还得退回去呢
Oh, tuck it back in, I have to return it.
好 记住我们的约定
Okay. Remember our deal.
我为你起床穿戴整齐 你得当我一辈子的奴隶
I got up and got dressed so you're my slave for life.
你们好呀 姑娘们
Oh, hi, girls.
我还以为你们是送希腊菜的外卖小弟呢
I thought you were the man with the Greek food.
我绝对要开始多给我的上唇去毛了
Wow, I have definitely got to start waxing my upper lip more.
苏菲 你不是在佛蒙特州吗
Sophie, why aren't you in Vermont?
我撒谎了
Oh, I lied.
我没有去佛蒙特州
I didn't go to Vermont.
那地方又远 而且我也不是同性恋啊
I mean, it's far and I'm not a lesbian.
我留在这里是为了监视奥列格
No, I stayed in town to spy on Oleg.
我知道你们俩觉得我很完美
I mean, I know you girls think that I'm perfect,
但我有信任问题
but I have trust issues.
那好吧 你住的是谁的公寓
Well then, whose apartment is that?
我住在阿健家呀
I'm staying at Jim's.
是直男阿健还是基佬阿健
Straight Jim's or gay Jim's?
苏菲 你忘了拿包包了啦
Sophie, you forgot your purse.
哎哟 这包包是我的吧
Oh, I think this is mine.
开玩笑啦 当然是你的啦
Just kidding, it's yours.
你们好呀 黑白无常
What's up, salt n' pepa?
是基佬阿健
Gay Jim's.
姑娘们 拜托不要告诉奥列格我在这
Oh, girls, please don't tell Oleg that I'm here.
你们也知道 我一直在跟踪他
You know, I've been following him around
看看我不在时他都会干什么
to see what he would do if I was not in town.
到目前为止 他都很乖
And so far, you know, he's been cool.
但古语有云
But you know the old saying:
"出轨一次 其错在你
"Cheat on me once, shame on you.
出轨两次 蛋蛋泡酒"
Cheat on me twice, your balls are in a jar."
天啊 咱们家门口居然站了一哥儿们
Oh, my god! There's a man standing in our doorway.
我又有门卫了
I have a doorman again.
这画面真奇怪 一个男人站在咱们家门口
Weird to see a man standing in our doorway
手里居然没拿着搜查令 驱逐令或圣经
without a warrant, an eviction notice, or a bible.
借过 这是我们的公寓
Excuse me, this is our apartment.
是啊 我们一直住在这里
Yeah, we live here all the time.
没什么大不了的
No biggie.
没什么大不了 没电 没租约
No biggie, and no electricity, no lease-y.
你好 我是卡洛琳 她是麦克斯
Hi, I'm Caroline. This is Max.
我们住在这里
We live here.
这名单上可不是这么说
Not according to the list.
先生 我们真的住在这里 我有"钥匙"呢
Sir, look, we do live here. I have a key.
"要人"都应该在名单上 但没有你们啊
The key is to be on the list, which you are not.
好吧 我可以证明我们住在这里
Okay, I can prove we live here.
你现在走到窗边 踹一脚暖气的侧面
Go over to the window, kick the side of radiator,
会有一个板子打开
a panel will open up.
里面有两根各抽过一半就掐掉的大麻烟
You'll find a half-smoked joint and another half-smoked joint.
-证明... -什么
- Proving-- - What?
你是一个穷鬼毒虫吗
That you're a poor pot head?
这真是太扯了
This is crazy.
我无法相信自己现在居然求着要回到一个
I can't believe I'm begging to get into a place
我之前一直拼命要逃离的地方
I've been trying to get out of.
里面可是一个非常私人的派对
It's a very exclusive party.
里面就是个垃圾堆
It's a dump.
我知道 因为我住这儿
I should know. I live here.
今晚真是惨得不能再惨了
This night couldn't get any worse.
快把灯关掉
Turn that light off.
我在用夜视镜看维密超模
I'm watching the Victoria's Secret super model party
开派对呢
with my night vision goggles.
惨度继续刷新
And updating.
奥列格 你是怎么进来的
Oleg, how did you get in here?
你觉得呢
How do you think?
这是我女朋友的公寓
It's my girlfriend's apartment.
当然是闯进来的啦
I broke in.
是啊 奥列格 这是你女朋友的公寓
Yes, Oleg, it's your girlfriend's apartment
而你却摸黑坐在这里
where you're sitting in the dark,
用夜视镜偷窥窗外的超模们
watching models out the window with night vision goggles.
怎么说话呢 老子穿着裤子呢
Hey! My pants are on!
放你的狗屁
No, they are not!
不怨我
Not my fault.
一想到楼下有五个维密的超模
Five Victoria's Secret super models downstairs?
老子的裤子自己扒了自己
They took themselves off.
这话什么意思 难道你还是受害人吗
So what are you saying? You're the victim here?
万一苏菲回来 看见你坐在这里
What would Sophie say if she came home
她会怎么说
and saw you sitting here?
她会说"别搞夜视镜了 搞我吧"
She'd say, "Stop hogging the goggles."
奥列格 我就这么说吧
Oleg, let me just say this:
佛蒙特州其实比你想象中要近
Vermont is closer than you think.
我不懂这有什么好吵的
I don't know where this argument is going,
但老子要下楼参加超模派对啦
but I'm going to that damn supermodel party.
奥列格 已经很晚了 我就直截了当地说吧
Oleg, it's late, I'm gonna lay this on the line for you.
你不是乔治·克鲁尼
You're no George Clooney.
你连乔治·克斯坦萨都不如
You're not even george costanza.
这床单超棒
These sheets are amazing
你永远也找不到比苏菲更好的女人了
and you are never gonna do better than Sophie.
她身材火爆
She is hot
而且显然她闻不到你的体臭
and clearly has no sense of smell.
我爱苏菲
I love Sophie.
我会乖乖回家
I'll go home.
转念一想 我还是不相信自己
On second thought, I don't trust myself
能心无邪念从你们家门口走过
to walk by your apartment.
把我锁在这里吧
Better lock me in here.
卡洛琳 麦克斯 快下来
Caroline! Max! Come down here! Hurry!
我就知道 听见了吗 麦克斯
I knew it! See, Max?
她们求着我们下去呢
They're begging us to come.
老娘重回时尚圈了
I'm back again.
你要一起来吗
Are you coming?
让我想想
Oh, let me think.
下楼尽情畅饮 或是在楼上
Downstairs with an open bar or up here,
跟小裤裤脏脏的奥列格独处呢
alone, with Oleg in his tighty-not-that-whities?
我们应该把你绑起来吗
Should we tie you up?
不必了 那只会更让我欲火焚身
No, it'll just make me hornier.
我就知道她们想让我们参加派对
I knew they wanted us to come to the party!
怎么可能不想呢
How could they not?
昨晚我教佩特拉吃面包的新方法
Last night I taught Petra how to eat bread
让她可以不用撕成一小块一小块吃
without tearing it into little pieces first.
想都别想 我可是海豹突击队的
Don't try it. I was a Navy Seal.
你觉得你很猛是吗
You think you're tough?
我曾在冰箱包装盒里住了一个月
I lived in a refrigerator box for a month.
不穿上衣哦[没有顶盖]
With no top.
不是包装盒 是我
Not the box. Me.
麦克斯 卡洛琳 快进来
Max, Caroline, get in here.
来了
Hey!
瞧 那就是我们的邀请函
See we were invited.
因为我们是大牌
'cause we're "A" list.
厕所堵了
The toilet is clogged
我需要你们处理一下 拜托了
and I need you to take care of it, please.
"大牌"指的是
"A list"
是打扫界的"大牌"人物吗
as in "A" janitor list.
我不知道该怎么办
I don't know what to do.
你们谁能帮忙叫下管理员吗
Can one of you call the concierge?
当然可以 卡洛琳
Sure. Caroline!
等等 等等 你们叫我们下来
Wait, wait, wait-- you didn't just call us down here
不是因为厕所堵了吧
'cause the toilet's clogged, did you?
不是
No.
那就好
Okay, good.
厨房水池也堵了
The kitchen sink is backed up, too.
厕所交给我处理
But, toilet, I got this.
我差点就在厕所出生的
I was almost born in one.
借过 借过 借过
Excuse me, excuse me, excuse me, excuse me.
好啦 大家淡定
All right, everyone just calm down.
无需惊慌
No need to overreact.
这是广告里提到的"泳池"
And there's the pool we mentioned in our ad.
天啊
Oh, boy.
没错 里面有几坨漂浮物
Yup, we got some floaters.
卡洛琳 我需要皮搋子和额叶切除手术
Caroline, I'm gonna need the plunger and a lobotomy.
老式厕所就这样
This happens with vintage toilets.
也算古色古香的魅力之一吧
Part of their old-world charm.
有些"魅力"沾到你的丝瓜络了
We got some charm stuck on your loofah.
姑娘们 还记得昨晚
Hey guys, remember last night
我们不用嘴嚼就能吃面包吗
how we just bit into that bread without chewing it?
勿忘美好时光
Good times.
快给我皮搋子 我可不想就这样"屎"掉
I need that damn plunger, I don't want to die this way.
找到了 但好像吸住什么东西了
Got it, but it's caught on something.
这到底是什么垃圾房子啊
What kind of a dump is this?
是你自己要体验威廉斯堡的生活
Hey! You wanted the Williamsburg experience,
这就是啊
this is it!
好消息 玛莎 我把你的直发器
Good news, Martha. I have your flat iron
恢复得跟以前差不多啦
looking pretty much back to normal.
太好了 留着吧
Oh, that's good. Keep it.
很抱歉弄脏了你的高级羊绒衫
Again, sorry about your cashmere sweaters in here.
但当时我们厕纸没了
But when we ran out of paper towels,
你的确喊了"随便用什么都行"
you did scream, "Just use anything, make it stop."
当然 我们会出钱送干洗的
And of course, we'll pay to have them all dry cleaned.
你们真好 留着吧
Oh, that's nice. Keep them.
好了 我们可以走了
Okay, we can leave.
我跟我的心理医生打完电话了
I am off the phone with my therapist.
不用你们说
And it goes without saying,
我们肯定也不会收你们的房钱
we won't charge you guys for this weekend.
不行 给
No way. Here.
务必收下这张支票和我心理医生的电话
You are taking this check and my therapist's phone number.
我真不知道没有他 你们怎么受得了这房子
I do not know how you are standing up without him.
拜托 这算什么呀
What? Come on, this is nothing.
地板还曾经真的张开嘴把我俩吞掉了呢
One month, the floor actually opened up and swallowed us.
是呀 我们遇到过更糟糕的情况呢
Yeah, we've been through worse.
你们俩相互支撑扶持的方式真酷
Oh, it's really cool the way you two support each other.
是啊 我们是一双"护"腿长袜
Yup, we're a pair of support hose.
说到"支撑"
And speaking of support--
给 麦克斯
Here, Max.
不是吧
No way!
瞧 卡洛琳 我的内衣大集合耶
Look, Caroline, it's a Bra-nanza!
卡洛琳 因为你实在没必要穿内衣
And, Caroline, since you don't really need to wear a bra...
给 这间公寓可能是地狱
Here. This apartment may be hell,
但你是一个真正的天使
but you are a real angel.
哇 属于我的翅膀
Aw, my own wings?
谢谢你们
Thank you, guys.
我能问你们一件事吗
Hey, can I ask you something?
只要跟老鼠无关的都行
As long as it doesn't have anything to do with rats.
你们为什么不邀请我们参加派对呢
How come you didn't invite us to the party?
什么 我以为玛莎邀请了呀
What? I thought Martha did.
我以为莉莉邀请了
I thought Lily did.
模特少根筋
Model moment!
上菜 卡洛琳
Pick-up, Caroline!
我就知道你会死在这里
Yup, I always knew you would die here.
上菜 麦克斯
Pick-up, Max!
看起来不错嘛 麦克斯
Looking good, Max.
你上完菜后 让卡洛琳进厨房
After you drop that, have Caroline come back here
把我关进冷库 等苏菲回来再放我出来
and lock me in the walk-in till Sophie gets home.
麦克斯 我刚意识到我们算是服务员界的超模
Max, I just realized we're kind of the supermodels of waitressing.
我也刚意识到 原来我的咪咪可以不用来回乱撞
And I just realized my boobs aren't always supposed to hit my side.